= kisskh.asia =
Characters, actions, places, occupations,
and events in this series
are fictional and created
for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge
or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Chan.
You are Chan’s ex?
I’m so sorry for putting you through this.
I love you.
Even though
you still don’t love me, it’s okay.
But I will always love you.
Mom.
Key.
What’s wrong?
Did you have a nightmare?
It’s okay.
Look at me.
Look into my eyes.
It’s okay. It’s just a bad dream.
Was the dream that scary?
Chan.
Why are you crying?
It’s just a bad dream.
Try to go back to sleep.
Here is your breakfast.
It will get tastier
if you get a kiss from me.
What?
Do you want another kiss?
Can you stop pretending
as if nothing happened?
Pretending?
About last night.
You had a nightmare.
It’s nothing.
It’s just a bad dream.
Everyone has a bad dream
from time to time.
Have you never had one?
Why are you this stubborn?
Chan, my cheek is all stretched out.
Can’t you give me a kiss instead?
You are so stubborn.
Fine.
I’ll tell you.
Last night,
I dreamt that you dumped me.
So I got scared.
Do you see how much I love you?
Are you sure that was the dream?
Yes.
Right, Simba?
It’s time for breakfast.
Come here and have breakfast with Mama.
Let’s eat breakfast.
Let’s have breakfast with Mama.
Come on.
Dig in.
Enjoy your meal.
Arrange her hair on the left.
Thank you.
Lift your chin a little.
Please arrange her dress.
Sun, lift your chin.
Sun, look at the mirror.
Look deep into the mirror.
Let’s take a break for 15 minutes.
I’m sorry, Peach.
I can’t really concentrate today.
It’s okay.
We all have days when we feel tired.
Please take a break. You will feel better.
I’m sorry.
Thank you.
Key.
What are you doing here?
When I heard that
you have a photoshoot with Sun today,
I rushed to see you.
You two know each other?
This is Key, my sister.
You’re not rushing off anywhere, are you?
Let’s go eat together after this.
Okay.
It’s really a small world, isn’t it?
Yes.
Since you are here,
can we talk?
Talk about what?
Something is bothering me.
Is it…
about Jay?
I will be abroad for one month.
I want you to take care of
my sister for me.
I already met her.
She suddenly came into Chan’s room.
Jay still has the keycard to Chan’s room?
This is not good.
I’ll tell Chan to change the keycard.
Otherwise, she will never
leave Chan alone.
I don’t think Chan will soften up easily
and take her back.
She seems so guarded, almost cold.
We never know, Key.
Chan is guarded and resolute.
But when it comes to Jay,
she always gives in to her.
That brat is always an exception for Chan.
Is it that serious?
Yes.
She is the type
who always gets what she wants,
no matter what it takes.
She is scary.
I don’t want to see my sister hurt again.
Sun, can you tell me?
What kind of person is Jay?
Miss Chan.
I prepared the details of the banquet
at the ballroom for you.
Can you check Mr. Kim’s proposal for me?
Sure, Miss Chan.
FOR MY MOON.
—YOUR J.
So you still remember
what my favorite flower is.
ARE YOU FREE TONIGHT?
DO YOU WANT TO WATCH ME SING?
I’LL THINK ABOUT IT.
IF I’M FREE, I’LL GO.
Let’s do our best like always.
Okay.
Hold the tempo for me.
Hello, Miss Chan.
You really came to see me.
You are so sweet.
I came to check if you are working hard.
Do you have any song you want to hear?
Any song is fine.
I’ll let you choose.
Please pick a song.
Please.
I want to sing the song for you.
The song that you sang
at my condo that night.
The song that you wrote.
Sure.
We’ll play ‘Your One’.
Hello.
Tonight,
we will start off with a special song.
It’s my self-composed song.
I wrote this song for someone,
someone important to me.
♪ If love is just a game
between you and me ♪
♪ I’ll make sure
I’m the one with the victory ♪
♪ I want everything my way,
make you agree ♪
♪ Your heart must belong to me ♪
♪ Just hold my gaze a little longer ♪
♪ Move your heart a little closer ♪
♪ Let’s take the meaning of love
a little further ♪
♪ What we have doesn't end tonight ♪
♪ I’ll love you every day ♪
♪ Close to me, your only one ♪
♪ I’ll make you love me,
make you remember ♪
♪ I’ll keep repeating till you surrender ♪
♪ With every touch, remember only me ♪
♪ I’ll hold you close in everything I do ♪
♪ Make it sink in, make you remember too ♪
♪ Slowly let your feelings run free ♪
♪ You’ll remember no one else but me ♪
♪ Ohh Ohh ♪
♪ Your only one ♪
Can I have a drink with you?
Yes.
What do you want?
Did you receive the flower from me?
I told my secretary
not to accept anything from you again.
It’s okay.
I can go and give it to you
myself next time.
I won’t ask anyone to do that for me.
You are still as self-centered as ever.
Back then,
we often listened to music together.
Do you remember it?
We had wine while listening to music.
It’s just the past.
Can you stop talking about the old days?
It won’t work on me.
That girl, Key.
Are you just sleeping with her?
Or are you thinking of
getting serious with her?
You told me
you didn’t like dating someone younger.
You liked dating someone
of the same age like me.
It looks like Chan is uncomfortable
with you touching her.
Key.
I thought you would avoid me.
I saw you walk down the stage and disappear.
I just went to get changed.
Sorry, Chan.
I changed out of the dress you bought me
for something else.
I guess you need to put effort into
your outfits.
Or Chan will get bored with you.
She never seems to get bored of me.
Right?
I don’t think we’ve officially
introduced ourselves.
I’m Jay.
Chan’s ex-girlfriend.
Nice to meet you.
I’m Key.
You can sleep around
or date someone to kill time.
I don’t mind it.
I understand.
Please take good care of my Chan, Key.
Don’t worry, Jay.
Good night.
Go get your stuff.
I’ll give you a ride back to your condo.
Don’t you want me
to stay with you tonight?
I have something to think about.
About Jay,
right?
You don’t need to pay attention to it.
It’s about you.
How can I not pay attention to it?
Pay attention to things involving you,
it’s my job.
Whoever makes you feel bad
or uncomfortable,
I will take care of them myself.
Can you really do that?
Of course.
I won’t let anyone
hurt you or make you sad.
I promise.
I will be your safe zone.
So you can also be a good girl.
You usually act like a stubborn girl.
I can be stubborn sometimes.
So you will want to pinch my soft cheeks.
Then…
Can I pinch your soft cheeks now?
Here.
You pinch it so often
that it’s almost bruised.
Because you always make me
want to pinch you.
I’ve done a lot for you.
But you still don’t want me
to sleep over at your place.
I’m sulking with you now.
Stop sulking.
Get it?
This is cheating.
That’s too bad.
You agreed to be my sugar baby.
So I’m the rule enforcer.
Fine, the rule enforcer.
So…
Can I spend the night with you?
Am I bothering you?
If I say you’re bothering me,
will you leave?
You can spend time comfortably at home.
I don’t get why
you want to follow me here.
I came here to take care of you
as your…
That’s enough.
You can do whatever you want.
Are you sure?
I can do whatever I want.
To be honest,
it’s quite exciting to do it here.
What are you doing?
I’m doing whatever I want.
You told me so.
This is my office.
Why don’t you rest your eyes a bit?
Is it your ex?
What’s up?
What do you call me for?
What are you doing here?
Where is Chan?
I heard that
you asked the hotel owner to serve you.
I suddenly feel eager to help her.
Here.
The mineral water that you ordered.
Chan also asked me to tell you
that she told her staff to arrange
the water for you every morning.
Is that so?
Okay.
Why don’t you take it?
Aren’t you thirsty?
Since you are here,
can you put it where I will use it?
Sure.
No problem.
Put it here.
Why?
I’ll use it to rinse my mouth.
Are you trying to get on my nerves?
What?
No, I’m not.
I rinse your mouth with mineral water
to hydrate it.
So my mouth won’t feel dry.
Has Chan never told you this?
She is the one who taught me this.
No.
I won’t follow the instruction either.
She set the no-kiss rule with you, right?
It means…
you and Chan
are not at the stage
where I have to be worried.
Do you think you can be her girlfriend?
All you can be is her sugar baby.
Yes.
I’m just her sugar baby.
I have never been her girlfriend like you.
But a sugar baby like me,
I’ve never hurt her.
Hey.
Can you stop sulking?
I don’t like it.
What do I need to do?
So you will like me.
You’re doing this again.
You’re acting like a child.
I’m just a child.
If you’re going to act
unreasonably like this,
you should go back to sleep
at your condo tonight.
You can scold me or act coldly towards me.
I’m okay with it.
But don’t chase me away
like I were an animal.
I’m also a human.
So this is my fault?
Okay.
It’s my fault.
I shouldn’t have done that.
I’ll sleep at my condo tonight.
Please take care of Simba.
We ran into each other quite often today.
I hope that we will become closer.
Are you two fighting because of me?
I think you know the answer.
I can’t help it.
This is how I am.
Why did you come back, Jay?
I came back to you.
I want us to get back together.
You suddenly left me.
Now you came back.
You expect me to simply forget
what you did to me?
What are you thinking?
Why are you so sure
that you can do anything to me?
Because I know
that you still love me.
You are just trying to deny it.
Yeah.
Fine.
I admit it.
I still love you, Jay.
So?
Let’s get back together.
I don’t want to get hurt by you again.
Please let me go.
I’m begging you.
Why are you drinking like this?
You are wasting it.
Wasting it?
I didn’t spill it.
Can I tell you the truth?
I really hit it off with you.
You know that?
Me too.
I did some digging about you.
At first,
I thought you were clinging
to Chan for money.
But you come from a well-known family.
Why did you agree to be her sugar baby?
If I tell you,
will you get out of Chan’s life?
Do you think I would do that?
I know you wouldn’t.
But I still want to ask you.
Maybe I’ll get lucky.
Do you like Chan that much?
I love her.
You two have known each other
for a short time.
Don’t you think it’s too fast
to say you love her?
No.
I’ve loved her for a long time.
Have you known her for a long time?
It happened
when my mom tried to abandon me.
My mom never loved me.
Why don’t you answer my call?
I’m scared.
Why are you not answering my call?
Mom, I’m scared.
Mom.
Mom, where are you?
I’m scared.
I’m really scared.
Mom.
Hey.
Are you alright?
I’m lost.
You’re lost?
What are you doing here alone?
I came to watch the stars.
Where are you going?
Do you want me to give you a ride?
It’s very dark here.
It’s dangerous to walk alone.
I want to go home.
Do you need a ride?
Where is your house?
In Bangkok.
Bangkok?
Do you want to ride with me?
I’m also heading back to Bangkok.
Come on.
I’ll give you a ride.
Did you see the picture I sent you?
(Yes.)
(The stars in Thailand are
much prettier than in the US.)
If it weren’t me,
who would take a long drive
to shoot a picture of stars for you?
(I know that
you will do everything I ask you.)
(Thank you.)
You are spoiled.
(I have to hang up. I’ve got to go.)
(Please hurry back.)
Alright.
(I miss you.)
When I’m done with my business,
I’ll hurry back.
(Love you.)
Love you too.
Do you want to use my phone
to call your family?
It’s okay.
Can you tell me why you are here alone?
What’s your name?
Key.
I’m Chan.
Chan as in the moon?
Yes, Chan as in the moon.
(If we can see the stars clearly
like tonight,)
it means we won’t see the moon.
On the night
when we can clearly see the moon,
we won’t see the stars.
Your name suits you well.
I don’t know what you’ve been through.
But you will get through it.
Stay strong.
Thank you.
Chan.
Thank you for giving me a ride.
It’s not a big deal.
You should go in. It’s late.
Yes.
Chan.
What?
When I’m older,
I’ll get a moon tattoo…
here.
Maybe one day,
our paths may cross again.
This will help you remember me.
I won’t forget you.
You should go inside.
Yes.
Drive safely.
Bye.
You know what?
Life…
Life can be so cruel sometimes.
Chan doesn’t remember me.
She’s never remembered me.
You are the only one she remembers.
She loves only you.
That’s why I can only be her sugar baby.
Are you going to give up?
No.
You don’t give up.
Neither will I.
Good.
That’s the spirit.
Now, you’re worthy of being my rival.
Are you going out to eat?
Can I come with you?
I don’t remember inviting you.
Do you feel intimidated by me?
I know that I hurt you when I left you.
But I also had no choice.
Don’t be sad, Chan.
I’m always your girl.
I want to be with you
and take care of you like this.
Between us is a business deal.
As long as the deal is still on,
you can still do your job.
If I fall in love with you for real,
what will you do?